

Ibnu Rijal **Al Qodri**Mathematics Education Students

- Kota Tangerang, Banten -Indonesia
- ☑ ibnurijalalqodri@gmail.com
- **%** +62 822 6018 5849

SOCIAL

- **f** @Muhammad Rijal
- @ @1911rijal0527
- @RijalQodri

PROFILE

I am a student majoring in mathematics education class of 2022 at Sultan Ageng Tirtayasa University. With a sense of responsibility and perseverance, I can finish work quickly. I have an interest in technology and mathematics, as well as some organizational experience and some achievements.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY LECTURE

Sultan Ageng Tirtayasa University Bachelor of Mathematics Education 2022 - Now

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

MAN 10 Jakarta Barat 2019 - 2022

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL

MTsN 27 Jakarta Barat 2016 - 2019

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

SDN Paninggilan 05 Ciledug

EXPERIENCE

MATH CLUB

From 2019 to 2020 | Member

With the initial aim to increase my knowledge and interest in mathematics, I joined this organization.

🌳 KELOMPOK ILMIAH REMAJA (KIR)

From 2019 to 2021 | Member

Curiosity and desire to gain knowledge in the field of science made me join this organization as a member only.

MATH CLUB

From 2020 to 2021 | Chairman

This year, alhamdulillah, I was entrusted with being the chairman of this organization so I also learned to be a good leader by continuing to carry out every activity even though I was still during the Covid-19 pandemic.

CERTIFICATES

Participated in Kompetisi Sains Madrasah (KSM)

I was once appointed as one of the school representatives in Kompetisi Sains Madrasah in the field of mathematics.

Participated in several competitions

I have participated in several math competitions from 2019 to 2021, although not as expected.

Became the head of the math club organization

Being chairman of the math club organization is an achievement that is enough to make up for my failures.

REFERENCES

My Mother

Mrs. Rini Mariani

Phone: +62 812-9130-5774 Email: rinimariani694@gmail.com

CHARACTERS

Discipline

Creative

Honest

Innovative

Hard Work

Responsible

Team Work

Mature

Patient

Persistent

SKILLS

- Html
- Css
- Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Microsoft Office
- Canva
- Capcut

LANGUAGES

- Indonesian English

INTERESTS

Music Jogging Football Game

+ -× = 88 Math Chess